厨房有哪些东西是我的？
Monica,which of all of this kitchen stuff is mine?
这个开罐器
This bottle opener.
还有呢？ 还有它也是个磁铁
-And...? -And it's a magnet.
你看
Look at that!
多巧啊
How weird is that? ...
你要搬来跟我住 而我就缺一个开罐器
You're moving in with me and you have the one thing I don't have.
仿佛是你让我变得完整
It's like,in a way,you complete me.
我是说厨房 什么？
-Kitchen. -What?
你让我的厨房变得完整，室友
You complete me kitchen,matey!
罗斯，我知道你在想什么 什么？
I know what you're thinking.
她搬去跟你住之后 或许会爱上你
That she'll move in with you,then fall in love with you,and then...
等她发现你们还有婚姻关系 就会很高兴
when she finds out you're already married,she'll be happy.
你真的很悲哀
You know? You're just very sad.
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
我终于知道了，你爱上瑞秋了
I see what this is. You are in love with Rachel!
什么？ 没错，这就对了，你迷恋她
It all adds up! You're obsessed with her. It's always:
“罗斯，瑞秋的事怎么办”
"What will you do about Rachel?
“罗斯，你为何要跟瑞秋住”
Why are you moving in with Rachel?
“你何时要承认没办注销” 你想要她
When will you confess your secret marriage to Rachel?" You want her!
乱讲
No!
电话救了你一命…你好
Saved by the bell.Hello
瑞秋，这对烛台不是我的吗？
Aren't these candlesticks mine?
不，那是我买的
No,I bought those.
对喔，我忘了
Oh,right. I forgot.
忘了你是个骗子
That you're a liar!
不会，太好了，我星期一过去 再次谢谢你，好的
That's great! I'll be there Monday. And thank you again.
是古生物学的系主任
That was the head of the paleontology department...
纽
at N...
约
Y...
大学
U.
他，说，什么？
Wow. What...did he...say?
记得我那篇沉积速率论文吗？
Remember that paper I had published last year on sediment flow rate?
他们很喜欢 有谁会不喜欢？
-They loved it. -Well,who wouldn't?
我知道
I know!
总之他们要聘我当客座教授
Anyway,they asked me to be a guest lecturer.
是暂时的
It's temporary,
但表现得好就可能转任正职
but if they like me,it could lead to a full-time job.
标在信箱上可帅了：盖勒教授
How great would that look on the mailbox? Professor Geller.
是啊，教授与夫人
Professor and Mrs.
与夫人？
And Mrs.?
对，你和罗斯还是夫妻
You and Ross are still married.
什么？
What?
开玩笑的啦
Just kidding!
哦上帝啊
Oh,God!
救了你的狗命
Saved your ass.
本集播出：“乔伊没了保险”
The One Where Joey Loses His lnsurance
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
怎么了？
What's the matter?
你知道我找的通灵者吧？ 是啊
You know that psychic I see?
她说我这个星期会死 所以我有点沮丧
She told me I'm gonna die this week,so I'm bummed.
什么？
What？
我知道你们不太懂通灵术 但这应该算是最糟的预言
I know you don't know about readings,but that's the worst you can get.
这太夸张了 她居然咒你死
That's crazy.She'd say that to you?
你不会相信吧？
You don't believe her,do you?
她预言过我会生三胞胎
I don't know. She said that I'd have triplets...
但她也说会有一个黑宝宝
but she also said one of them would be black.
纯属好奇：她有提到死法吗？
Just out of curiosity,did she say how you'd go?
没有，她到最后才告诉我
She didn't tell me I'd die till the end of the session.
我不想再跟她耗1小时
I wasn't gonna waste a whole other hour there!
我只剩1星期了 我得开始享受人生
I've only got a week left.I've really gotta start living now!
（汽车与驾驶）
大家好
Hey,everyone.
我今天第一次上课
Well,today's my first lecture...
想找你们演练一下，可以吗？
and I wanted to try it out on you guys. Do you mind?
好啊 没问题
No,that'd be great!
沉积速率有三个主要理论
"There are three primary theories concerning sediment flow rate.
每一个还可以细分为两个…
Each of these theories can be further subcategorized into two..."
我就是这样死的
This is it. This is what's gonna kill me.
类别，第一个是…
"...subcategories. The first of these subcategories is.."
罗斯，你那张纸上有裸女吗？
Are there naked chicks on that piece of paper?
没有，怎么了？
No. Why?
我没见过纸上没有裸女 男人还会死盯着看
I never seen a guy stare so hard at something that didn't have chicks on it.
好…
okay
沉积速率有三个主要理论
"There are three primary theories concerning sediment flow rate.
每一个还可以细分为两个…
Each of these theories...can be further subcategorized into
不如以笑话开场
Why don't you open with a joke?
以笑话开场？ 那是大学，不是夜总会
Open with a joke? It's a university,not a comedy club.
等一下，且慢
Wait a minute,hold the phone.
是咯咯窃笑大学吗？
You're not talking about Chuckles University?
好
okay
开玩笑的啦
Come on,we're kidding.
你知道怎样会比较不无聊？ 谢谢你喔
You know what might make it less boring?Thank you.
运用影像辅助
Some visual aids.
你知道哪种影像辅助最好？ 别跟我说裸女
-You know what's a good visual aid? -Don't say naked chicks.
为什么不行？
Why not?
真不知道我干嘛找你们商量
I don't even know why I talk to you guys about it.
我自己解决，不必用裸女
I'm just gonna do it on my own,with no naked chicks.
我19岁之前就是那样
That's the way I did it till I was 19.
好吧，20岁
All right,20.
23岁
Twenty-three.
有有用的信吗？ 有，演员工会寄信给你
Any good mail?Something from the Screen Actors Guild.
可能是重播费 你帮我拆一下，我…
It's probably a residual check. Can you open it? I got....
保险中止
"Benefits lapsed."
怪了，我没记得演过这部片
That's weird.I don't remember being in a movie called Benefits Lapsed
这不是支票 你的健康保险失效了，因为…
It's not a check. Your health insurance expired because...
你去年的工作时数不够 我看看
-you didn't work enough last year. -Let me see that.
不会吧，真糟糕
Oh,I can't believe this!This sucks!
有保险时我可以被车撞 或是被火烧
When I had insurance,I could get hit by a bus...or catch on fire,you know?
都无所谓，现在却得小心？
And it wouldn't matter. Now I gotta be careful?
真可惜，被火烧这种事… 停了总是不好
I'm sorry. There's never a good time to have to...stop catching on fire.
好吧，我得找工作了 我去见经纪人
All right,well...I guess I gotta go see my agent.
过马路要小心左右来车
Make sure to look both ways before you cross the street.
"Make sure to look both ways before you cross the street."
菲比，你还活着
Hey,you're still alive!
感觉如何？ 等死好累喔
How are you feeling?It's so exhausting,waiting for death.
对了，你能不能…
Oh,by the way,do you think you..
菲比，你干什么？
What are you doing?
我在替你做心理准备…
Preparing you for..
你没有以为我死了吗？ 我装得不像吗？
Didn't you think I was dead?Did that not come off?
像，我吓死了 我还以为我们永别了
Yeah,scared the hell out of me. I thought we'd lost you forever.
你要不要睡一下？ 好，谢谢
-You wanna lie down? -Yeah,thanks.
对了，帮我一个忙
Can you do me a favor?
两个小时后叫我 如果还叫得醒的话
Wake me up in a couple hours.You know,if you can.
莫妮卡
Monica
这是你放回去的？
Did you take these back?
不是，我很喜欢 就去买了一对
I liked them so much that I bought some for myself.
真的很好看对吧？ 我爱死它们了
They're really great,aren't they?I love them.
想耍诈
Nice try.
课上得怎样？ 很顺利
How'd the lecture go?It went great.
既不需要笑话，也不需要裸女
And I didn't need any jokes or naked chicks either.
太好了 抱歉之前没有好好帮忙
That's great. I'm sorry we weren't supportive before.
我就知道教材充实最重要
I knew I just had to let the material speak for itself.
每个人都说 “你得表现得风趣又性感”
Everyone's all,"Ross,you have to be funny and sexy."
我证明他们错了
Well,I proved them wrong!
我现在就去告诉乔伊和钱德
And now I'm gonna pass the news on to Joey and Chandler.
说你不风趣也不性感的消息吗？ 没错
-That you're not funny or sexy? -That's right!
艾斯黛，听着…
-Hey,Estelle,listen.. -Well,well,well.
乔伊崔比亚尼，回来了是吧？
Joey Tribbiani.So you came back,huh?
每个人都以为走比较好 但最后都爬回来求艾斯黛
They think they can do better,but they all...come crawling back to Estelle.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我哪有离开 你一直是我的经纪人
I never left you. You've always been my agent.
是吗？ 是啊
Really?
我没恶意，你别在意
Oh,well,no harm no foul.
艾斯黛，你得帮我找工作 我的保险没了
Look,you gotta get me some work. I lost my health insurance.
好，首先得控制损失 为什么？
All right,first thing we gotta do: damage control.-Why?
我觉得可能有人在城里到处给你造谣呢
-Well,I think...someone out there may have been bad-mouthing you all over town.
畜生
The bastard!
（纽约大学）
我们来早了 还有15分钟才下课
We're early. The lecture doesn't end for 15 minutes.
我们可以溜进去看 好
-But we could sneak in and watch. -Yeah,we could.
看，“背靠背”姐妹会的人 我以前也是
Hey,look. There's some Kappa Kappa Deltas. I was a Kappa.
嗨 姐妹们
Hey,sisters.
我们还真是犯贱
Wow,we really are bitches.
好，瑞格比从实验室 取回样本后
Right. So when Rigby got his samples back from the laboratory...
有了惊人的发现
he made a startling discovery.
他原以为那是火山物质 其实是沉积物
What he believed to be igneous was,in fact,sedimentary.
想象一下他有多震惊吧…
Imagine his consternation when..
糟糕
Oh,bloody hell.
明天艾斯黛帮我排了一堆试镜
So Estelle lined up a bunch of auditions for me tomorrow.
我很快就能重新加入保险
And I'll have my health insurance back in no time.
太好了 但你现在应该去蹲马桶吧？
That's great,but shouldn't you be on the toilet right now?
什么？ 你是怎么了？
-What's wrong with you?
没什么，我刚才举哑铃时 肚子突然一阵剧痛
-Nothing.I got this blinding pain in my stomach when I was lifting weights before.
然后就昏倒了 而且一直站不起来
And then I passed out...and I haven't been able to stand up since.
不过应该没什么
But I don't think it's anything serious.
这应该是疝气，你得去看医生 我才不要
This sounds like a hernia. Go to the doctor.No way.
就算要去看医生 也是因为肚子这里突出来
If I go to the doctor,it'll be for this thing sticking out of my stomach!
那就是疝气
That's a hernia.
我为什么要恢复健身？
Why'd I have to start working out again?
该死的哑铃
Damn you,15s!
你在搞什么？
What the hell are you doing?
我很紧张 你们害我担心我会很无聊
Look,I was nervous.You guys had me all worried I was gonna be boring.
我上了台，学生都盯着我看
I got up there and they were all,like,staring at me.
结果我一开口就是英国腔了
I opened my mouth and this British accent just came out.
而且还很不正宗
Yeah,and not a very good one.
别再说了
Will you,please...?
盖勒博士，我是寇特拉斯曼 古生物学系教授
Dr. Geller? Kurt Rathman.I'm a paleontology professor here.
可以聊聊你的课吗？
Do you have a moment to talk about your lecture?
抱歉，我和我妹妹有事要办
I'm sorry,I've got plans with my sister.
莫妮卡盖勒
Monica Geller.
是的，失陪一下
Right. Will you excuse us for one moment?
你干什么？ 你能装我就不能装？
-What are you doing? -You can have an accent,but I can't?
女士们早啊
Top of the morning to you,laddies!
别闹了
Would you just please stop?
是的，这个季节的孟买非常漂亮（印度腔）
Yes,yes,Bombay is very,very nice this time of year.
帮我点个小煎饼
Hey,will you grab me a cruller?
坐下啦
Sit down!
我拜托你去看医生
Will you go to the hospital?
大哥，疝气手术…应该很贵
Hernia operations cost...a lot probably,okay?
而且它越来越黑，越来越痛 就表示有在好
Besides,it's getting darker and more painful. That means it's healing.
我借你钱，赶快去医院把它… 塞回去
Look,I'll loan you the money.Just go to the hospital and let's just get that thing...pushed back in.
谢谢，但我要很久才能还你 我不想惦记这件事
Thank you,but it'd take me forever to pay you back.I don't want that hanging over my head.
而且只要保险恢复 我就可以动各种免费手术
Besides,when my insurance kicks in...I can get all the free operations I want.
我打算先去做激光眼科手术
I'll probably start with that laser eye surgery.
怎么了？
What's going on?
乔伊的疝气很严重 不过动个激光眼科手术就好了
Joey's got a hernia,but it's nothing a little laser eye surgery won't fix.
真的，把手压在这里就还好
I'm telling you,if I put my hand on my stomach...it doesn't hurt that bad.
搞不好你会死
Hey,maybe you'll die!
钱德，我怕了
Chandler,I'm scared.
我们可以一起走
No,we can go together.
但不要拖太久 我星期五之前就会挂掉
Just don't wait too long,because I'm out of here sometime before Friday.
但是我不想死
But I don't want to die.
不，会很好玩 我们可以回来吓他们
It'll be fun. We'll come back and haunt these guys!
等等，我可以趁莫妮卡和瑞秋洗澡时回来吗？
Wait. Could I come back and haunt Monica and Rachel when they're in the shower?
那是我的女朋友 嘿，我都已经死了
-That's my girlfriend. -Hey,I'm dead!
给我 不要，这是我的
-Give me them! -No,they are mine!
是你偷我的 你才偷我的
-You stole them from me! -You stole them from me!
拿来
Give me them!
要不要一人一个？
Just wanna each take one?
很公平，反正也从来没用过
Yeah,that seems fair. We never use them.
听着，你们真的得帮我
Look,I really need some help,okay?
为什么我要说英国腔？
Why did I have to speak in a British accent?
我该怎么办？ 去问妈咪和爹地呀
What do I do?Why don't you call Mummy and Daddy?
我说真的，我迟早会被揭穿 教书的事就泡汤了
I'm serious! Someone's gonna find out and then they're never gonna offer me a job.
慢慢把口音改掉 别人会以为你在适应美国生活
Why don't you phase it out? Yeah,phase the accent out.People will think you're adjusting to life in America.
是啊，根本不会有人注意 搞不好根本没人在听你讲什么
Come on. No one will even notice.They're probably not even listening to you.
没人在听我讲话？ 当然有，每个人都在听你讲话
They're not listening to me?Of course they're listening to you.Everybody listens to you.
你真的觉得我要慢慢改吗？
Monica,do you think I should try this phasing-out thing?
我觉得你很好啊
I think you look fine.
好了就开始 好
Whenever you're ready.
提米，我要给你一个惊喜
Hey,Timmy.I've got a surprise for you.
停，抱歉 这个惊喜是一组新秋千
Hold it. I'm sorry.The surprise is a new swing set.
别演得这么凝重 好，没问题，等我一下
If you could play it less intense.Oh,yeah. Sure,no problem.Just hold on one second.
提米，我要给你一个惊喜
Hey,Timmy.I've got a surprise for you!
天哪
Oh,my God!
所以我都喂我的狗吃普瑞纳一号（雀巢旗下的宠物食品品牌） 今天就去买一包吧
So that's why I feed my dog Purina One.Pick up a bag today.
这时候你要把它搬起来 没错
-That's where you pick up the bag. -Exactly.
不是，台词是搬一包 所以你得把它搬起来
The line is,"Pick up a bag," so you need to pick up the bag.
或者，我可以指着它
Or I could just point to it.
什么什么，普瑞纳一号 今天就去指一包吧
Purina One. Point to a bag today.
我没通过，对吧？
I didn't get it,did I?
没有 好
No. okay
你好，我是乔伊崔比亚尼 我来试镜，演个男人
Joey Tribbiani.I'm here to audition for "Man."
垂死的人吗？ 没错
You mean "Dying Man."
快，再打一次 真的要打？好
-Do it one more time. -Really? Really? Okay.
罗斯你好 我是假口音大学的麦尼利博士
Hello,Ross? This is Dr. McNeely from the Fake Accent University.
我们想聘你当专任教授
We'd like you to come onboard full-time!
听我说 预言错了，我不会死了
Listen to this!My reading was wrong. I'm not going to die.
真的？你怎么知道？ 因为我的通灵者死了
Really? How do you know?My psychic is dead!
她一定是看错牌了
She must have read the cards wrong.
我很遗憾 总比我死好
I'm sorry.Better her than me.
我们来烤饼干
Hey,let's bake cookies!
恭喜你拿到这个角色 谢谢
Listen,I'm really glad you got the part.
你真的能演吗？ 能
Are you sure you can do this?
谢谢你陪我来 还有谢谢你帮我洗澡
And thanks for coming with me.And thanks again for helping me take a shower.
这算是我们说好的绝口不提吗？
Now,is that "never talking about it again"?
乔伊，都准备好了
We're ready for you.
这是阿历克斯，他演你的儿子 你好
This is Alex. He'll be playing your son.Hi,Alex.
我的手可没塞在裤子里
As you can see,my hands are not in my pants.
好
okay
阿历克斯，当乔伊说到 “好好照顾你妈妈”
All right,Alex. Now,when Joey says his line..."Take good care of your mama,son,"
你就要哭，懂吗？ 好，来吧
that's your cue to cry. Got it?All right,let's do this.
第五场，第一次
Scene five,take one.
开始
And action!
儿子，好好照顾你妈妈
Take good care of your mama,son.
拜托啦，你妈是个好人
Come on,son.Your mama's good people.
停，阿历克斯，这里应该要哭 你这次可以哭吗？
Cut! Alex,remember,you're supposed to cry.Can you cry for us this time?
好吧 好，重来
All right. From the top.
第五场，第二次
Scene five,take two.
第三十六次要来了
Take 36 is up.
再来一次，乔伊，你好了吗？
Let's try this again.You ready,Joe?
请问一下，你喊开始前 我可以大叫吗？
One thing,is it all right if I scream...right up until you say,"Action"?
可以
Sure.
开始 儿子，好好照顾你妈妈
-Action! -Take good care of your mama,son.
停
Cut!
打扰一下…乔伊，你把衣服掀开来 小鬼你看
I'm sorry. Why don't you lift up your shirt? Take a look at this,kiddo.
他哭了，摄影机快拍
We have a crying child! Roll the damn cameras!
罗斯在吗？ 他不在，你要留言吗？
-Hello,is Ross there? -No,he's not. Can I take a message?
好，我是罗斯的离婚律师
Yes,this is Russell,Ross' divorce lawyer.
我一直没有他的答复 我想他应该是想试着经营这段婚姻
Since I haven't heard from him,I assume he's giving the marriage a try.
罗斯又结婚了？不~~
Ross got married again?
（继续，慢慢改掉口音）
All right,keep going. We are phasing the accent out.Phasing it out.
要不是进实验室重新化验结果
"So without retesting their results in the laboratory...
研究小组也不会发现
the team would never have identified...
原先的碳14定年结果有误
the initial errors in their carbon dating...analysis."
到这里有问题吗？
Were there any questions at this point?
请说 你的口音怎么没了？
What's happening to your accent?
再说一次，你说什么？
Come again? What's this nonsense?
好吧，我不是英国人 我是长岛人
All right. I'm not English.I'm from Long lsland.
我一紧张就冒出那个腔调了 很抱歉
I was really nervous,and the accent...just came out.I'm sorry.
回到课堂上来
So if we could just get back to the lecture.
有任何问题吗？
Were there any questions?
关于古生物学的问题？
About paleontology?
我只是想留下良好的第一印象 但我显然搞砸了
I was just trying to make a good first impression.Obviously,I screwed up.
但你们对我的看法很重要 因为我想成为专任教授
But what you guys think of me is important because I'm hoping to get a permanent job here.
如果你们肯再给我一次机会给你们留下好印象的话…
So if you'd just give me another chance to make a good impression..
罗斯！你疯了吗？ 我还是你的老婆？
Ross! Are you crazy?I am still your wife?
你想瞒我一辈子吗？ 你是哪里有病？
Were you just never gonna tell me?What the hell is wrong with you?
我真想宰了你
I could just kill you!
瑞秋你好
Well,hello,Rachel!
你真的玩过？ 真的
You've really done this before?
你就用力打下去，不要手软 好
You just take a big,big swing,okay?Now,don't hold back.
你们在干嘛？ 庆祝乔伊的保险恢复
What are you doing?We're just celebrating that Joey got his health insurance back.
好
Oh,all right.
看吧，脱掉头盔再来一次
See? Now let's try one without the helmet.